movewith.com 2019-04-05

# The Best Audio Fitness Classes From Cardio to Strength to Meditation | MoveWith

Last updated: May 25, 2018

### INTRODUCTION

MoveWith, Inc. ("MoveWith," "we" or "us") provides an online and mobile service, the MoveWith website, www.MoveWith.com (the "Site"), computer mobile applications ("App" or "Apps") and programs hosted by or on behalf of MoveWith and related services (together with the Site and the Apps, the "Service"). The terms "you" and "user" means all individuals and entities that access the Service. MoveWith offers audio fitness classes from top trainers that you can take anytime, from anywhere.

### SUMMARY

This privacy policy explains the types of personal data we collect and how we use and protect that information:

  * Scope
  * Information We Collect 
  * Our Use Of Your Information
  * Data Retention
  * How We Share Your Data
  * Your Rights
  * Payments
  * Third Party Websites
  * MoveWith Blog
  * Changes to the Policy
  * Contact and Queries

### SCOPE

This Privacy Policy describes how we use Personal Information (defined below) that we collect from you as part of you using our service. This Privacy Policy also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update this information, and what information you provide that we will retain even if you decide to delete the App or stop using the Service. Our Privacy Policy is not a contract, and it does not create any legal rights or obligations.

You should also read our Terms of Service, available at [www.movewith.com/terms](https://www.movewith.com/terms) which contains important information about the scope and nature of the Service, and the rules that apply to your use of our Service. All capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given to them in the Terms of Service for MoveWith.

Your use of the Service indicates that you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information and other information as described in this Privacy Policy and the MoveWith [Terms of Service](https://www.movewith.com/terms). If you do not consent to the use of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy or do not agree to the Terms of Service, do not use the Service.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect the following types of information from and about you:

General:

  * Your contact details. Your name, postal address and other contact details, such as your telephone number and e-mail address.
  * Your account data and electronic identification data (including data added thereto). Your MoveWith account ID and other electronic identification data (such as IP address or other device identifiers) and the data you add to your MoveWith ID account, such as your password, your date of birth, your gender, your picture and other information you may share with us.
  * Information regarding your use of our online Services. This may include data regarding the pages you visit, your internet connection, your computer or mobile device and software you use, how frequently you exercise and what types of activities you prefer
  * Your reviews. The opinions, experiences, preferences and interests that you publish on our website, our app or share with us online
  * Your communication data. Your requests, any complaints you may have and any other data that we receive if we communicate with you via e-mail, online or via social media.

We also collect information you voluntarily provide to us in relation to your physique, condition or nutrition in order to customize and enhance your experience when using our products and Services. These personal data may – by itself or in combination – reveal information about your (physical) health. The special categories of personal data include:

  * Activity data and other information you provide when using the Services or information that is provided via the Apple HealthKit API. Personal measurement information and activity data that you voluntarily share with us through the use of the Services, including but not limited to weight, height, age, heartrate, calories burned, steps taken, nutritional information, sleep activities, other activity data (type, duration and frequency of fitness activities, distance, speed, pace, step count).

In addition, when using our Services, we may also collect information regarding your location with respect to country of origin and time zone.

Below, we describe the specific types of information we collect from our users including you.

#### Account Information

When you create an account, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your name, username, password, postal address, and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account on the Service and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you, and therefore, you may not be anonymous.

We may use your contact information to send you information about our Service or to receive marketing emails. Our marketing emails tell you how to "opt-out." If you opt-out, we may still send you non-marketing emails. Non-marketing emails include emails about your account and our business dealings with you. We may also contact you when we believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes.

#### User Content

Some features of the Service allow you to submit User Submissions to the Service. All User Submissions submitted by you to the Service may be retained by us so long as you use the Service or maintain an account. We may also retain User Submissions submitted by you for a short period after you terminate your account. We may continue to disclose such User Submissions to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. By submitting any User Submissions, you agree that such User Submissions is non-confidential for all purposes. In addition, your User Submissions is posted and transmitted at your own risk. Although, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Service with whom you may choose to share your User Submissions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Submissions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

#### IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically

We automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Site, including your IP address and cookie information. Generally, the Site automatically collects usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of the Service so that we can analyze and improve them.

#### Cookies, Analytics and Personalization

We and our third party providers use cookies, clear GIFs/pixel tags, JavaScript, local storage, log files, and other mechanisms to automatically collect and record information about your browsing activities, and use of the Services. We may combine this "activity information" with other personal data we collect about you. Generally, we use this activity information to understand how our Services are used, track bugs and errors, improve our Services, verify account credentials, allow logins, track sessions, prevent fraud, and protect our Services, as well as for targeted marketing and advertising, to personalize content and for analytics purposes.

  * **Do-Not-Track (DNT)** : Please note we do not respond to browser do-not-track requests. You may, however, disable certain tracking as discussed in the applicable Cookie Policy.
  * **Detailed Cookie Policy** : 
    * "Cookies" are small data files that are sent to your web browser when you access a website, and the files stored on your device's hard drive. We use "session" cookies to keep you logged in while you use the Site, to track your preferences and to track trends and monitor usage and web traffic information on the Site. These are erased when you close your browser. We use "persistent" cookies to relate your use of our Service to other information about you and store information about your preferences to make your user experience consistent and customized. For example, we may create a persistent cookie that includes some basic information about you, like your favorite website locations and whether customer support responded to your inquiry. These cookies stay on your hard drive until you erase them or they expire and associate your information with your account even if you are logged out.
    * Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your settings on the browser settings to refuse cookies or prompt you before accepting cookies. You can also use your browser settings or other tools to delete cookies you already have. However, if you disable or refuse cookies, then certain features of the Site may be inaccessible or not function properly.
    * Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Service and may associate that information with your account if you have one.
    * Certain features of the Site may use local shared objects (or "flash cookies"). Flash cookies are small files similar to browser cookies that collect and store information about your preferences and where you browse and what you look at on the Site. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser or device settings that are used for browser cookies. You may adjust your Adobe Flash Player settings to prevent flash cookies from being placed on your hard drive.
    * This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer.
    * We may use "clear GIFs" (aka "web beacons" or "pixel tags") or similar technologies, on our Service or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a part of our Service or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a website or in an email or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote website on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual's viewing or receipt of a website or message.
    * We do not automatically collect Personal Information, but we may tie Personal Information with the automatically collected information using the above tools or information collected from other sources.
    * We may also log information using digital images called web beacons on our Service or in our emails. We may use web beacons to manage cookies, count visits, and to learn what marketing works and what does not. We may also use web beacons to tell if you open or act on our emails.

#### Biometric and AppleHealth Kit Information

When using our iOS App, and specifically the integrated AppleHealth Kit API, you grant us permission, unless you have opted out, to collect certain information including but not limited to your biometric data which may include but is not limited to your steps, heart rate and other physical activity. We will use this information to help improve class recommendations and track your workout activity by sending and receiving data to and from Apple's HealthKit Application. Your data and information generated by and stored in the AppleHealth Kit API will not be furnished, published, or sold to any third parties for advertising and/or marketing purposes.

#### Children Under Age 13

We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register on our Service. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, please contact us at [support@movewith.com](mailto:support@movewith.com). In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information where reasonably possible.

### OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Information other than Health Related Information, to: 

  * provide to you and communicate with you about the services, content, features or products you use or request;
  * customize and optimize the content or advertisements you receive when you use the Service, and otherwise improve your experience on our Service;
  * analyze and improve our Service, which may include tracking traffic, usage, and navigation patterns related to your activities on the Service and the links we provide to Third Party Websites or advertisements;
  * secure your account and prevent fraud;
  * carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;
  * protect our or third-party rights or interests;
  * in any other way we may describe when you provide the information; and
  * for any other purpose with your consent.

### DATA RENTENTION

If you delete the App, close your account or stop using the Service, we will retain your identifying information and continue to use any information you have already provided to us unless you send us an email to [support@movewith.com](mailto:support@movewith.com) from the address associated with your account asking that we delete your identifying information, in which case we will delete your identifying information, but retain any other information you provided for use without reference to your identity.

### HOW WE SHARE YOUR DATA

#### Sharing Information with Third Parties

We may share your personal data with the following parties:

  * **Service Providers and Processor**. We engage third party vendors, agents, service providers, and affiliated entities to provide services to us on our behalf, such as support for the internal operations of our websites, payments (including payment processors for purchases via our website or app related payments via Apple iTunes), Services (e.g., technical support processing, analytics), as well as related offline product support services, data storage and other services. In providing their services, they can access, receive, maintain or otherwise process personal data on our behalf. Our contracts with these service providers do not permit use of your information for their own (marketing) purposes. Consistent with applicable legal requirements, we take commercially reasonable steps to require third parties to adequately safeguard your personal data and only process it in accordance with our instructions.
  * **Partners** : We may share Personal Information with our business partners in order to provide you a service you use or request, subject to commitments by such parties to use your information only for that purpose and to protect it from disclosure.
  * **Third parties in case of legal requirement**. We may share Personal Information in response to a valid law enforcement request or legal process, to protect our rights and property or those of third parties, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.
  * **Corporate transaction** : We may share Personal Information with a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of MoveWith's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information held by MoveWith about our Service users is among the assets transferred.
  * We may also share with third parties aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot be reasonably used to identify you, including for marketing and research purposes or for sale to interested parties.

Additionally, in the following circumstances, we may disclose your Personal Information without your consent:

  * if we believe there is a serious and imminent threat to the life, health or safety of yourself or another person (for example, if we learn that a person is suffering abuse or has made statements of an intent to commit self-harm or harm another);
  * to investigate or report on activity which we believe on reasonable grounds to be unlawful;
  * if disclosure is required or authorized by law (for example, in response to a subpoena or where a regulatory authority has the power to request the provision of certain records or information);
  * if disclosure is reasonably necessary to enable an enforcement body to perform its functions, for example the prevention, detection, investigation, prosecution or punishment of criminal offenses, or the preparation for, or conduct of, proceedings before any court or tribunal, or implementation of the orders of a court or tribunal; or
  * if we deem it necessary in our sole discretion to protect our legal and legitimate business interests.

### YOUR RIGHTS

You have the following rights concerning your personal data: right of access, right of rectification, right to erasure, right to restrict data processing, right to object against profiling and your right to data portability. If you would like to contact us regarding any of these rights please email us at [support@movewith.com](mailto:support@movewith.com).

#### Accessing and Modifying Your Information

You will have the opportunity to review and modify the information stored in your account profile any time you log onto your account using the username and password listed on the account. You can also control MoveWith's access to Apple's Health Kit information via the settings on your phone.

#### How to opt-out

If you choose to stop receiving emails from MoveWith, please follow the unsubscribe instructions within each email communication, log into your MoveWith account to manage your email communication preferences or send an email to [support@movewith.com](mailto:support@movewith.com). MoveWith will not provide or share any mailing lists or other information about you to another company or service for promotional purposes. Any service related emails (to confirm a purchase, etc.) generally do not offer an option to unsubscribe as they are necessary to provide the service you requested.

#### Protecting Your Information

We take the security of your Personal Information very seriously, and have implemented policies and procedures, including technical measures, that are designed to help safeguard it. Please remember that you play a valuable part in security as well. Your password to access our Service, which you select at registration, should never be shared with anyone and should be changed frequently. While we strive to use best practices to protect your Personal Information, the Internet and computer technology is not 100% secure and we cannot absolutely ensure the security of any Personal Information that you provide to us.

#### California Residents

California residents may choose to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes or choose to opt out of such disclosure. To make a request or to opt out at any time, please contact us at [support@movewith.com](mailto:support@movewith.com) or the other contact information provided below. Our policy is not to disclose Personal Information collected online to a third party for directing marketing without your approval.

### PAYMENTS

For purchases made on our website ([www.movewith.com](https://www.movewith.com/)), MoveWith uses Stripe as its third party service provider for payment services (e.g. card acceptance, merchant settlement, and related services). By purchasing or leading an Activity you agree to be bound by Stripe's Privacy Policy: <https://stripe.com/us/privacy> and hereby consent and authorize MoveWith and Stripe to share any information and payments instructions you provide with Stripe and other third party service provider(s) to the minimum extent required to complete your transactions.

For purchases made through Apple iTunes (e.g., if you download MoveWith's app for iPhone and purchase a subscription via the app), you agree to be bound by Apple's Privacy Policy: <https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/>.

### THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

You should carefully review security/privacy policies of any third party sites accessible from the Site. Other sites accessible through the Site have their own policies and data collection, use, and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's policies and practice. MoveWith is not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. The information practices of those websites linked from the Site are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information.

### MOVEWITH BLOG

MoveWith hosts its online Blog on Medium, a site that can be accessed through <https://medium.com/movewith> (the "Blog"). Any Personal Information you provide on the Blog is stored by the outside service provider. Any Personal Information submitted on the Blog is subject to Medium's privacy policy. You can access the privacy policy [here](https://medium.com/policy/medium-privacy-policy). MoveWith recommends that you read that privacy policy before submitting any Personal Information on the Blog. If you use the Blog, you should be aware that any Personal Information you submit in the comment field can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums indefinitely, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. MoveWith is not responsible for the Personal Information you choose to submit via the Blog.

### CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. It may be necessary from time to time for us to modify this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the way we collect and use information or changes in privacy-related laws, regulations, and industry standards. Accordingly, we reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting the revised policy on this Service and updating the "last modified" date at the top of this page. If the changes are material, we will include "recently updated" next to the link to this policy on the Site and the App. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. If revisions to the Privacy Policy are unacceptable to you, you must stop using this Service.

### CONTACT MOVEWITH

The Service is owned, operated, and maintained by:

MoveWith, Inc.  
590 Howard Street  
San Francisco, CA 94105 

MoveWith welcomes your questions and comments about security and privacy. Please send any questions or comments via email to [support@movewith.com](mailto:support@movewith.com).
